[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "How much are the eggs?",
        "options": [
            "1.25 pound",
            "1.50 pound",
            "2 pounds"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1.50 pound"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What time does the train leave? (for him to go on a business trip)",
        "options": [
            "9.45",
            "8.45",
            "9.15"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "9.15"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "How does she go to school?",
        "options": [
            "She walks",
            "She drives",
            "She goes by bus"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "She walks"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "A woman is calling her husband. What time is lunch ready?",
        "options": [
            "1pm",
            "2pm",
            "3pm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2pm"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What does she usually do in the evening?",
        "options": [
            "listen to music",
            "go for a walk",
            "go to the coffee shop"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "go for a walk"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Where will they meet?",
        "options": [
            "at the university",
            "at the station",
            "at the park"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "at the park"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What does this family do most weekends?",
        "options": [
            "goes with their friends",
            "goes bowling",
            "goes for a walk"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "goes for a walk"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What day do they meet?",
        "options": [
            "Tuesday",
            "Thursday",
            "Friday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What career did he choose?",
        "options": [
            "to work in business",
            "to be a teacher",
            "to keep studying"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to work in business"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What course did he take?",
        "options": [
            "Management",
            "Computer",
            "Leadership"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Computer"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "A woman is talking about her job. How is being a writer different from other jobs?",
        "options": [
            "She works irregular time",
            "She does not have a high salary",
            "She has no fixed workplace"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "She works irregular time"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Where does she buy food?",
        "options": [
            "at a local market",
            "at a convenient store",
            "at a new shopping centre"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "at a new shopping centre"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What causes air pollution?",
        "options": [
            "Fire from the countryside",
            "Pollutants from private cars",
            "Smoke from factories"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fire from the countryside"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What time do they meet?",
        "options": [
            "7.30pm",
            "6.30pm",
            "9.30pm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "6.30pm"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "What time does she meet her child?",
        "options": [
            "Seven o'clock",
            "Three o'clock",
            "Two o'clock"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Three o'clock"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "What does her sister drink?",
        "options": [
            "Water",
            "Tea",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tea"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "How many buildings will the town have?",
        "options": [
            "1000",
            "2000",
            "3000"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2000"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "What does she usually do on Saturdays?",
        "options": [
            "plays sports",
            "goes to the park",
            "sees her family"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "sees her family"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "What do they both buy?",
        "options": [
            "Books",
            "Trousers",
            "Clothes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Clothes"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What color shirt did he buy?",
        "options": [
            "Blue",
            "Black",
            "Red"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "When is the assignment due?",
        "options": [
            "on Friday",
            "on Saturday",
            "on Thursday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "on Saturday"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What did the professor want her to do?",
        "options": [
            "Do research",
            "Make a report",
            "Speak at the conference"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Speak at the conference"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Where did she choose to go on holiday?",
        "options": [
            "The south",
            "The park",
            "The mountain"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The south"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "What is special about the new song?",
        "options": [
            "The singer",
            "The words",
            "The melody"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The words"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "What did she like the most about the movie?",
        "options": [
            "the car scenes",
            "the fight scenes",
            "the mountain scenes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the mountain scenes"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Why did she become a scientist?",
        "options": [
            "a large stone",
            "her dream",
            "her favorite collection"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a large stone"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "What time will they meet?",
        "options": [
            "Half past eight",
            "Quarter to seven",
            "Quarter to eight"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Quarter to eight"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Where did they meet for the bus home?",
        "options": [
            "hotel entrance",
            "bus station",
            "market place"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "market place"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "How old is Stephanie?",
        "options": [
            "21",
            "22",
            "23"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "21"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Where is the club near?",
        "options": [
            "A park",
            "A library",
            "A coffee shop"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A park"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "What to feed the cat?",
        "options": [
            "Milk",
            "Fish",
            "Cat food"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Fish"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What does this family do most weekends?",
        "options": [
            "goes with their friends",
            "goes bowling",
            "goes for a walk"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "goes for a walk"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "What does he need to buy for his sister?",
        "options": [
            "Chocolates",
            "Eggs",
            "Milk"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Chocolates"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "The train was delayed. What time does the train leave?",
        "options": [
            "8.45",
            "9.15",
            "9.30"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "9.30"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Which area has the best weather?",
        "options": [
            "In the south",
            "In the east",
            "In the west"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "In the east"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Why was the museum visit cancelled?",
        "options": [
            "Join other activities",
            "Poor weather conditions",
            "Not enough people"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Not enough people"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Where is the cafe?",
        "options": [
            "Next to the station",
            "Near the gift shop",
            "Opposite the gift shop"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Opposite the gift shop"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Where is the tea served?",
        "options": [
            "The building",
            "The river boat",
            "The museum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The river boat"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Which room is the largest in her house?",
        "options": [
            "Living room",
            "Bedroom",
            "Kitchen"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Kitchen"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "What time is the meeting?",
        "options": [
            "9.15",
            "10.15",
            "10.30"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10.15"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "Why did he call his friend?",
        "options": [
            "To make an appointment",
            "To say hello",
            "Suggest a drink"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Suggest a drink"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "How does he feel?",
        "options": [
            "Sick",
            "Sad",
            "Well"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sick"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "What is the mother asking her daughter to buy?",
        "options": [
            "eggs",
            "chocolates",
            "bread"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "eggs"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "When do they meet?",
        "options": [
            "8.00",
            "9.00",
            "10.00"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10.00"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Why can't she pick up her child?",
        "options": [
            "meet her client",
            "have an urgent meeting",
            "stay late at the office"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "stay late at the office"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "What movie does she recommend?",
        "options": [
            "comedy film",
            "action film",
            "horror film"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "action film"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "A man is calling his friend. Where is he?",
        "options": [
            "the park",
            "the station",
            "the town hall"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the town hall"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "What means of transport does he use to get to work?",
        "options": [
            "by bus",
            "by train",
            "by car"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "by bus"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "What time do experts recommend eating fruit?",
        "options": [
            "in the morning",
            "in the afternoon",
            "in the evening"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "in the morning"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Why does she wake up early?",
        "options": [
            "to exercise",
            "to have some quiet time",
            "to do housework"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to have some quiet time"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "Why is he learning to drive?",
        "options": [
            "driving a car is his dream",
            "he hates public transport",
            "he has to drive to work"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "he has to drive to work"
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "What does he buy directly at the shop?",
        "options": [
            "Books",
            "Clothes",
            "Trousers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Clothes"
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "How much did he pay for the computer?",
        "options": [
            "350 pounds",
            "150 pounds",
            "250 pounds"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "250 pounds"
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "What did they bring for the picnic?",
        "options": [
            "clothes",
            "fruit",
            "food"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "food"
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "What colour is the teacher's house?",
        "options": [
            "Blue",
            "Red",
            "White"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "White"
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "What time is the football match?",
        "options": [
            "1pm",
            "7pm",
            "4pm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1pm"
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "What does she do on her holidays?",
        "options": [
            "Drawing",
            "Walking",
            "Cooking"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Walking"
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "Why does she like the manager?",
        "options": [
            "He was good at his job",
            "He paid her a lot",
            "He taught her a lot"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "He taught her a lot"
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "What does he want to be?",
        "options": [
            "Reporter",
            "Chef",
            "Writer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Writer"
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "What does he drink?",
        "options": [
            "Tea",
            "Juice",
            "Water"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "What does he remember most about his school days?",
        "options": [
            "Homework",
            "History classes",
            "Teachers"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "History classes"
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "What will she do?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the coffee shop",
            "Go for a drive",
            "Go on a picnic"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Go for a drive"
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "What does she have in common with her mother?",
        "options": [
            "They look like each other",
            "They have similar interests",
            "They have similar characteristics"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "They have similar interests"
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "What does he buy at the shop?",
        "options": [
            "a suit for the office",
            "a dress for his wife",
            "new clothes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a suit for the office"
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "What do birds do in winter?",
        "options": [
            "They look for food reserves",
            "They stay in groups for protection",
            "They migrate to other regions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "They stay in groups for protection"
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "Why did he call his friend?",
        "options": [
            "To make an appointment",
            "To say hello",
            "Suggest a drink"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Suggest a drink"
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "How much does the smallest car cost?",
        "options": [
            "1250 pounds",
            "2250 pounds",
            "3250 pounds"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "3250 pounds"
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "A woman is calling her friend. What did she lose?",
        "options": [
            "Phone",
            "Bag",
            "Key"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Phone"
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "What did he forget?",
        "options": [
            "Money",
            "Phone",
            "Glasses"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Glasses"
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "How many Americans are there?",
        "options": [
            "one",
            "two",
            "three"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "one"
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "Which room is her favourite?",
        "options": [
            "Bathroom",
            "Kitchen",
            "Bedroom"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bathroom"
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "Where did they go last year?",
        "options": [
            "Camping",
            "Cycling",
            "Bowling"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Camping"
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "What subject does her son like to study?",
        "options": [
            "Science",
            "Art",
            "Math"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Art"
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "What does she usually do in her free time?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the theatre and play sports",
            "Play sports and go shopping",
            "Stay at home and shop online"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Go to the theatre and play sports"
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "What advice do they need for decorating their living room?",
        "options": [
            "How to buy a sofa",
            "Where to buy cups",
            "Where to buy a new table"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Where to buy a new table"
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "What is his opinion on train travel?",
        "options": [
            "Convenient",
            "Friendly",
            "Practical"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Practical"
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "What is not original?",
        "options": [
            "Furniture",
            "Door",
            "Window"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Furniture"
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "What number do you press to buy a new computer?",
        "options": [
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Three"
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "Where does she walk every night?",
        "options": [
            "The university area",
            "The park",
            "The college"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The college"
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "How many chairs do they need to prepare for a meeting?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "20",
            "30"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "20"
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "Where did she ask the coffee shop to look for her lost item?",
        "options": [
            "On the sofa",
            "In the corner",
            "On the table"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "In the corner"
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "Where did they meet?",
        "options": [
            "The parking lot",
            "The front entrance",
            "The school gate"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The front entrance"
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "The daughter is calling her father. What did she buy?",
        "options": [
            "Trousers",
            "A dress",
            "Glasses"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A dress"
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "There will be a school party soon, what should the teacher prepare?",
        "options": [
            "Prepare drinks",
            "Arrange the seat",
            "Order the food"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Order the food"
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "When will she need a computer?",
        "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Thursday",
            "Monday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Friday"
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "What country will they study next semester?",
        "options": [
            "France",
            "Italy",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "France"
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "What do they need to repair for the building?",
        "options": [
            "Windows",
            "Doors",
            "Gate"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Windows"
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "What does the actor like to do?",
        "options": [
            "Jogging",
            "Swimming",
            "Drawing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Drawing"
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "What new thing is being built at the school?",
        "options": [
            "A stadium",
            "A Performance space",
            "A school yard"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "A Performance space"
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "What does he like about Dubai?",
        "options": [
            "He gets a higher salary",
            "He enjoys the weather here",
            "He enjoys his job here"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "He enjoys his job here"
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "What does he advice young people to do to save money?",
        "options": [
            "Cook for yourself",
            "Save money",
            "Buy things online"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cook for yourself"
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "Which room will they study in?",
        "options": [
            "Room 201",
            "Room 301",
            "Room 302"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Room 301"
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "What time is the football match?",
        "options": [
            "1pm",
            "7pm",
            "4pm"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1pm"
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "What is the phone number of the shop?",
        "options": [
            "20 10 30",
            "10 20 30",
            "30 10 20"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "20 10 30"
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "What did they bring for the picnic?",
        "options": [
            "clothes",
            "fruit",
            "food"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "food"
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "How many copies did he sell?",
        "options": [
            "Over 300000 copies",
            "100.000 copies",
            "30.000 copies"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Over 300000 copies"
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "Where did they go last year?",
        "options": [
            "Camping",
            "Cycling",
            "Bowling"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Camping"
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "What do they plan to do together?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the coffee shop",
            "Make plans later",
            "Have dinner together"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Make plans later"
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "What does the man drink?",
        "options": [
            "Water and iced tea",
            "Water",
            "Iced tea"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Iced tea"
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "Who did she take the picture of?",
        "options": [
            "The girl's team",
            "The boy's team",
            "Anna, Sara and the girl's team"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The girl's team"
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "Where do they go when they travel to India?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the park",
            "Go to famous places",
            "Go out to eat"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Go to the park"
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "What is the weather like today?",
        "options": [
            "Cold and not wet",
            "Hot and wet",
            "Cold and wet"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cold and wet"
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "How did he adjust the meeting?",
        "options": [
            "cancel the meeting",
            "having the meeting without him",
            "having the meeting another day"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "having the meeting without him"
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "Which door do they need to take to get to Edinburgh?",
        "options": [
            "Two",
            "Three",
            "Four"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Two"
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "How does he feel?",
        "options": [
            "Sick",
            "Sad",
            "Well"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sick"
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "How long does it take to get to the station?",
        "options": [
            "15 minutes",
            "20 minutes",
            "25 minutes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "20 minutes"
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "What did he call to say?",
        "options": [
            "to say hello",
            "to meet Felix",
            "to say thank you"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "to say thank you"
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "Who is coming to visit him this weekend?",
        "options": [
            "His mother",
            "His sister",
            "His sister and her children"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "His sister and her children"
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "What time is the meeting?",
        "options": [
            "2pm",
            "10am",
            "11am"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2pm"
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "Why can't she pick up her child?",
        "options": [
            "meet her client",
            "have an urgent meeting",
            "stay late at the office"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "stay late at the office"
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "How much do the cleaning products cost?",
        "options": [
            "one pound fifty",
            "two pounds",
            "one pence"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "one pound fifty"
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "Where is she going with her family?",
        "options": [
            "The mountains",
            "The lake",
            "The park"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The mountains"
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "What did he usually do last year?",
        "options": [
            "Running",
            "Cycling",
            "Walking"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Cycling"
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "How many minutes did he have to speak?",
        "options": [
            "10",
            "15",
            "25"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "15"
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "Who does she live with?",
        "options": [
            "Her colleague",
            "Her sister",
            "Best friends"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Best friends"
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "Why does she want to be a writer?",
        "options": [
            "Help people",
            "Make money",
            "Her dream"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Help people"
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "Why was the flight canceled?",
        "options": [
            "There are no flight staff",
            "Plane maintenance",
            "Poor weather conditions"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Poor weather conditions"
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "Why did he call his friend?",
        "options": [
            "To make an appointment",
            "To say hello",
            "Suggest a drink"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Suggest a drink"
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "When did they decide to meet?",
        "options": [
            "7am on Friday",
            "9am on Sunday",
            "9am on Saturday"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "9am on Sunday"
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "A girl is calling her mother. Which dress does she want?",
        "options": [
            "long and green",
            "long and red",
            "short and red"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "long and red"
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "What day is the new appointment?",
        "options": [
            "Thursday 13th",
            "Tuesday 13th",
            "Wednesday 10th"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Thursday 13th"
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "A man is calling his wife. Where did they meet?",
        "options": [
            "At the park",
            "At the station",
            "Outside a shop"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Outside a shop"
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "What did she do last weekend?",
        "options": [
            "Stayed at home",
            "Went shopping",
            "Went to the cinema"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Stayed at home"
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "How many weeks have they been in India?",
        "options": [
            "1 week",
            "2 weeks",
            "3 weeks"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "2 weeks"
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "Where is the office?",
        "options": [
            "Opposite the hotel",
            "Near the park",
            "Opposite the station"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Opposite the hotel"
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "Where do they wait for the bus?",
        "options": [
            "Next to the hotel",
            "Near the hotel's main entrance",
            "By the hotel's main entrance"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "By the hotel's main entrance"
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "What does his wife like to do?",
        "options": [
            "sightseeing",
            "going shopping",
            "photography"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "photography"
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "What outdoor activities do they do in the afternoon?",
        "options": [
            "Play golf",
            "Go to dance classes",
            "Play bridge"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Play golf"
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "A women is introducing a concert. The concert will end with?",
        "options": [
            "A surprise performance",
            "Some special offers",
            "The city's favorite group"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The city's favorite group"
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "What was the writer's first job?",
        "options": [
            "cook",
            "reporter",
            "teacher"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "teacher"
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "What does her sister drink?",
        "options": [
            "Water",
            "Tea",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tea"
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "What is the population of this village?",
        "options": [
            "10000",
            "2000",
            "5000"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "10000"
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "Where does he want to go tomorrow?",
        "options": [
            "The town hall",
            "The city center",
            "The museum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "The town hall"
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "What floor is the office on?",
        "options": [
            "on the first floor",
            "on the second floor",
            "on the third floor"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "on the first floor"
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "When can they play football at school?",
        "options": [
            "Friday afternoon",
            "Wednesday afternoon",
            "Thursday afternoon"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Wednesday afternoon"
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "Where is the office?",
        "options": [
            "Opposite the hotel",
            "Near the park",
            "Opposite the station"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Opposite the hotel"
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "A man is calling his wife. Where did they meet?",
        "options": [
            "At the park",
            "At the station",
            "Outside a shop"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Outside a shop"
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "What time do he have dinner these days?",
        "options": [
            "6 o'clock",
            "7 o'clock",
            "8 o'clock"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "7 o'clock"
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "What does he do after work?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the coffee shop",
            "Play football",
            "Go home"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Play football"
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "What did they both like about the movie?",
        "options": [
            "the characters",
            "the ending",
            "the plot"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the ending"
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "What area is he describing?",
        "options": [
            "a university area",
            "a park",
            "a library"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "a university area"
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "A man wants to buy a new house. What is his biggest problem?",
        "options": [
            "choosing the proper area",
            "financial problems",
            "persuading his family"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "persuading his family"
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "When do they meet each other?",
        "options": [
            "On Thursday morning",
            "On Wednesday morning",
            "On Tuesday morning"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "On Thursday morning"
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "How old is this city?",
        "options": [
            "150 years",
            "1500 years",
            "2000 years"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "1500 years"
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "What colour is Jack's house?",
        "options": [
            "Red",
            "Black",
            "Green"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "What does her sister look like?",
        "options": [
            "Short",
            "Tall",
            "Thin"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Short"
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "What did he usually do last year?",
        "options": [
            "Running",
            "Cycling",
            "Walking"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Running"
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "How does he travel?",
        "options": [
            "by train",
            "by car",
            "by bus"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "by train"
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "How long does it take her to ride her bike?",
        "options": [
            "35 minutes",
            "25 minutes",
            "20 minutes"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "35 minutes"
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "What does she usually do in her free time?",
        "options": [
            "Go to the theatre and play sports",
            "Play sports and go shopping",
            "Stay at home and shop online"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Go to the theatre and play sports"
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "Which sports is she good at?",
        "options": [
            "Running",
            "Swimming",
            "Football"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Football"
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "What are the similarities between his mom and aunt?",
        "options": [
            "They were thin",
            "They have the same eye color",
            "They have the same hair color"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "They were thin"
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "What time does she usually write?",
        "options": [
            "In the evenings",
            "In the afternoons",
            "In the mornings"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "In the afternoons"
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "What did she advice for people who lack motivation at work?",
        "options": [
            "quit the job",
            "ask for a salary increase",
            "request a transfer"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "request a transfer"
    }
]